[
  {"question"  : "C",
   "answer"    :["c3","i2","inter","i3"],
   "hint"	   : "",
   "id"        : 0 
  },
  {"question"  : "A ∧ B ∧ C",
   "answer"    : ["inter"],
   "hint"	   : "By associativity...A ∧ B ∧ C = (A ∧ B) ∧ C = A A ∧ (B ∧ C)",
   "id"        : 1
  },
  {"question"  :"A ∧ B",
   "answer"    : ["i1","inter"],
   "hint"	   : "",
   "id"        : 2  
  },
  {"question"  :"¬C",
   "answer"    : ["c1","c2","i1","uni"],
   "hint"	   : "",
   "id"        : 3 
  },
  {"question"  : "¬(A ∨ B ∨ C)",
   "answer"    : ["uni"],
   "hint"	   : "",
   "id"        : 4
  },
  {"question"  : "A → B",
   "answer"    : ["c2","c3","i2","i1","inter","uni"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... ¬A ∨ B ",
   "id"        : 5
  },
  {"question"  :"A → C",
   "answer"    : ["c2","c3","i2","i3","inter","uni"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... ¬A ∨ C ",
   "id"        : 6  
  },
  {"question"  :"(A ∧ B) → C",
   "answer"    : ["c1","c3","i2","i3","inter","uni"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... ¬(A ∧ B) ∨ C ",
   "id"        : 7 
  },
  {"question"  : "(A → B) ∧ (B → C)",
   "answer"    : ["i2","c3","inter","uni"],
   "hint"	   : "Draw the truth table!",
   "id"        : 8
  },
  {"question"  :"Awesome!",
   "answer"    : [""],
   "hint"	   : "PLEASE PROVIDE FEEDBACK",
   "id"        : 9  
  }
]

